<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jahun Lee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Jahun Lee</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:26:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:26:48 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[2_Research]]></title><description><![CDATA[My research focuses on urban governance, particularly on how local governments make choices regarding collaboration with third parties. I examine patterns and mechanisms of collaboration between local governments and other actors to understand how these arrangements shape service delivery and governance outcomes.
Research interests: urban governance; local governments; collaboration; service delivery; network analysis; and urban shrinkage.
Figure 1. Map of Research Interests and Projects Dissertation: The Choice of Service Delivery Mode (TBD) Status: in progress
Advisor: Dr. Michael Siciliano
Methods: mixed methods (conjoint experiment and in-depth interviews)
Short description: (research question / data / methods, 1 line) IGOs in Korea (TBD) Status: in progress
Methods: STERGM (Separable Temporal Exponential Random Graph Model)
Short description: (research question / data / methods, 1 line) The Tiebout Model under Urban Shrinkage in Korea (TBD) Status: in progress
Methods: MR-QAP (Multiple Regression Quadratic Assignment Procedure)
Short description: (research question / data / methods, 1 line) **Master’s thesis (2018). A Study on the Reconceptualization of Sharing and a Case Analysis of the Sharing Economy (Korean Title: 공유의 재개념화와 공유경제 사례분석: 서울시 자동차 공유사례를 중심으로) Advisor: Dr. Tae Young Kim
This study pertains to collaboration among individuals in urban contexts. Since the 2010s, "sharing" has become a rhetorical device in marketing and public policy, carrying connotations of community. However, its multiple and ambiguous meanings often generate debate. This study clarifies the concept of “sharing,” develops an ideal-typical framework, and applies it to a case analysis of car-sharing in Seoul, drawing on literature from anthropology, sociology, and business. This study provides insights by distinguishing different dimensions of “sharing,” particularly behaviors (allocation and commoning practices) and states of possession and ownership, and examining their implications. 김정욱, 이왕기, 이자훈. (2021). 인천광역시 제2기 마을공동체 만들기 기본계획 (The Second Master Plan for Community Building in Incheon Metropolitan City), 인천광역시. -Kim, J., Lee, W; Lee, J. (2021). The Second Master Plan for Community Building in Incheon Metropolitan City (Original title: 인천광역시 제2기 마을공동체 만들기 기본계획). Incheon Metropolitan City. ]]></description><link>2_research.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2_Research.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:26:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HOME]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a Ph.D. Student in Public Administration at <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" target="_self">the Department of Public Policy, Management and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago (UIC)</a>. I am an affiliated student of the Networks and Governance Lab at UIC.Hi! My name is Jahun Lee, and&nbsp;I am an Ph.D. Student in the Department of Public Policy, Management, and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago. My research focuses on urban governance, in particular, how local governments interact with others, including other governments, private organizations, particularly nonprofits, to enhance their performance and improve outcomes for their communities. Currently, I have interests in the influence of demographic shifts on urban governance. ]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3_Other Activities]]></title><link>3_other-activities.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3_Other Activities.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1_About]]></title><description><![CDATA[Test pages
title: University of Illinois Chicago
date: Aug. 2021 - Current
description: Ph.D. in Public Administration title: University of Seoul
date: Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2018
description: Master in Public Administration ]]></description><link>1_about.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1_About.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>