<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jahun Lee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Jahun Lee</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:33:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:33:47 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Publication]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Lee, M. &amp; Lee, J. (2025). Assessment of Jeju's Regional Conditions Using the Balanced National Development Index and Policy Implications. Society for Jeju Studies. 64. 223-246. 10.47520/jjs.2025.64.223. Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Merriman, D., Hu, X., Lee, J., Worthington, P.&nbsp;(2026).&nbsp;Current Condition and Future Concerns for Growth in Illinois’ State
Merriman, D., Funderburg, R. Hu, H., Lee, J., Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Worthington, P. (2025) The State of Illinois’ FY 2024 Fiscal Situation: A Solid Performance but Threats Remain.&nbsp;<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588" target="_self">https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588</a>
]]></description><link>publication.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Publication.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a Ph.D. Student in Public Administration at <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" target="_self">the Department of Public Policy, Management and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago (UIC)</a>. I am an affiliated student of the Networks and Governance Lab at UIC.Hi! My name is Jahun lee, and&nbsp;I am an Ph.D. Student in the Department of Public Policy, Management, and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago. My research focuses on local governance, in particular, how local governments interact with others to enhance their performance and improve outcomes for their communities.
This includes relationships with other governments, private organizations, particularly nonprofits.Currently, I have interests in the influence of demographic shifts on local governance. <br>I received my PhD in Public Administration and Public Policy at the School of Public Affairs at Arizona State University, where I worked as a research associate at the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="http://www.csteps.asu.edu/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="http://www.csteps.asu.edu/" target="_self">Center for Science, Technology, and Environmental Policy Studies</a>&nbsp;(C-STEPS).&nbsp;Before moving to the US, I lived in Italy, Paris and Brussels. I got my MPA from University of Seoul (Korea).&nbsp;<br>You can find out more about my&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://fusifederica.weebly.com/my-research.html" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://fusifederica.weebly.com/my-research.html" target="_self">research</a>&nbsp;by navigating this website.]]></description><link>hello-world.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Hello World.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Research Interest]]></title><description><![CDATA[ title: "Research Interests"
description: | My research primarily focuses on urban governance which consists of various choices of different actors. Particularly, I concentrate on collaborations of local governments with third parties
to understand patterns and mechanisms in urban context. title: "Projects in Development"
ref: "Lee, J. Local public managers’ choice of service delivery mode" ]]></description><link>work-in-progress/research-interest.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Work in Progress/Research Interest.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Test]]></title><description><![CDATA[Test pages
title: University of Illinois Chicago
date: Aug. 2021 - Current
description: Ph.D. in Public Administration title: University of Seoul
date: Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2018
description: Master in Public Administration ]]></description><link>test.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Test.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>