<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jahun Lee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Jahun Lee</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:47:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:47:12 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[3_CV]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="mailto:jlee903@uic.edu" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="mailto:jlee903@uic.edu" target="_self">jlee903@uic.edu</a>
University of Illinois Chicago, Chicago, Illinois, USA (Aug. 2021 - Present) Ph.D. student in Public Administration
Committee: Michael Siciliano (Chair), Jered Carr, Kelly LeRoux, Kate Albrecht, Jill Tao University of Seoul, Seoul, Korea (Feb. 2016 - Feb. 2018) MPA in Urban Administration
Advisor: Tae Young Kim Myongji University, Seoul, Korea (Mar. 2007 - Aug. 2014) BA in Public Administration Research Assistant, Institute of Government and Public Affairs (Aug. 2024 - Present)
Researcher, Incheon Institute&nbsp;(Mar. 2020 - Jan. 2021; Apr. 2021 - Jul. 2021) Lee, M. &amp; Lee, J. (2025). Assessment of Jeju's Regional Conditions Using the Balanced National Development Index and Policy Implications. Society for Jeju Studies. 64. 223-246. 10.47520/jjs.2025.64.223. Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Merriman, D., Hu, X., Lee, J., &amp; Worthington, P.&nbsp;(2026).&nbsp;Current Condition and Future Concerns for Growth in Illinois’ State.
Lee, M., Jeong, J., Lee. S., &amp; Lee, J. (2025). A Commissioned Study on Mutually Beneficial Cooperation and Regional Development between the Lava Seawater Industrial Complex and Surrounding Communities (Written in Korean, Korean title: 용암해수산업단지와 주변 마을의 상생협력 및 지역발전 방안 연구 용역). Jeju Institute
<br>Merriman, D., Funderburg, R., Hu, H., Lee, J., Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., &amp; Worthington, P. (2025). The State of Illinois’ FY 2024 Fiscal Situation: A Solid Performance but Threats Remain.&nbsp;<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588" target="_self">https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588</a>
Choi, T., Kim, J., &amp; Lee, J. (2021). 인천광역시 일자리 사업 성과평가시스템 구축, 인천광역시.
Kim, J., Lee, W., &amp; Lee, J. (2021). The Second Phase Master Plan for Community Building in Incheon (Written in Korean, Korean title: 인천광역시 제2기 마을공동체 만들기 기본계획), Incheon Metropolitan Government.
Kim, J., Jang, J., Lee, J., &amp; Lee, Y. (2020). Management Plan for the Community-Building Intermediary Organization in Michuhol District (Written in Korean. Korean title: 마을공동체 중간지원조직 운영방안), Incheon Institute; Michuhol District ARNOVA
ARNOVA-ASIA
MPSA
ASPA
UAA
]]></description><link>3_cv.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3_CV.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1_About]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a Ph.D. student in Public Administration at University of Illinois Chicago studying urban governance and collaboration in public service delivery.My research examines governance across multiple levels, from community-level collaboration to interorganizational and intergovernmental arrangements.For more details on my research, please see the <a class="internal-link" data-href="2_Research" href="2_research.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Research page</a>.
I am affiliated with the Networks &amp; Governance Lab (NGL) at UIC.
<br>I work as a research assistant at the Institute of Government and Public Affairs (IGPA), where I contribute to the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://igpa.uillinois.edu/igpa-data-hub/fiscal-futures" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://igpa.uillinois.edu/igpa-data-hub/fiscal-futures" target="_self">Fiscal Futures Project</a>, focusing on the integration and analysis of Illinois state government fiscal data. I was a researcher at the Incheon Institute in Korea (2020–2021), working on community-building initiatives and employment policy evaluation.
I served as a council member at a solar energy cooperative in Korea (2013)
I was involved in a nonprofit organization focused on environmental justice in Korea (2013) Last updated: Feb. 2026
]]></description><link>1_about.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1_About.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HOME]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ph.D. Student, Public Administration
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa/" target="_self">Department of Public Policy, Management, and Analytics</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://uic.edu" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://uic.edu" target="_self">University of Illinois Chicago</a>
<br>Affiliated Student, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa/net-gov-lab/" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa/net-gov-lab/" target="_self">Networks &amp; Governance Lab</a>
<br>Research Assistant, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://igpa.uillinois.edu" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://igpa.uillinois.edu" target="_self">Institute of Government and Public Affairs</a>
<br>✉️ <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="mailto:jlee903@uic.edu" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="mailto:jlee903@uic.edu" target="_self">jlee903@uic.edu</a>]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:47:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2_Research]]></title><description><![CDATA[My research focuses on urban governance as it emerges from interactions among multiple actors—including public authorities, for-profit firms, nonprofit organizations, and individuals—under varying institutional and contextual conditions. I examine how patterns of collaboration among these actors shape governance processes and outcomes.More specifically, my recent work investigates how actors’ choices at different levels are conditioned by institutional arrangements, interorganizational relationships, and broader contextual environments.Figure 1 presents a conceptual map of my research interests, illustrating how actor choices are embedded in governance arrangements and shaped by environmental contexts.
Keywords　urban governance · local governments · collaboration · service delivery · social network analysis · urban shrinkage
Figure 1. Conceptual Map of My Research Interests
Status: in Progress
Methods: Mixed methods (conjoint experiment and in-depth interviews)
Description: This dissertation examines how local governments choose among alternative service delivery modes (in-house provision, contracting out, and hybrid arrangements) as well as partners, under varying institutional, relational, and contextual conditions, with a focus on police patrol and road maintenance services.
Urban shrinkage—marked by sustained population loss, economic decline, and physical deterioration—constitutes a governing context rather than a discrete policy problem.Rather than focusing on shrinkage as a discrete policy problem, this perspective shifts attention from policy instruments to how governance arrangements, collaboration, and conflict evolve under sustained demographic and structural constraints. While public administration has long examined government responses to fiscal stress and economic downturns, comparatively less attention has been paid to how such long-term demographic and structural change shapes governance choices and interorganizational relationships.The studies presented below examine how demographic shifts shape governance dynamics. I focus empirically on South Korea, an early and extreme case of urban shrinkage, which allows examination of these dynamics under long-term structural constraints that are increasingly observed in advanced economies: Formation and Dissolution of IGOs in Korea (TBD) Status: Writing
Description: Shrinking cities face reduced capacity and diminished amenities, potentially increasing incentives for intermunicipal collaboration. This study examines how urban shrinkage shapes the formation and dissolution of intergovernmental organizations (IGOs) in Korea, focusing on administrative consultative councils as a key institutional form of interlocal cooperation. Research Question:&nbsp;Does urban shrinkage affect intermunicipal cooperation? Methods: STERGM (Separable Temporal Exponential Random Graph Model) Conference presentation: Lee, J. (2026). APSA Lee, J. (2026). UAA The Tiebout Model under Urban Shrinkage in Korea (TBD) Status: Writing
Description: This study revisits the Tiebout model in the context of urban shrinkage, examining whether population flows in Korea continue to reflect differences in local public service bundles under nationwide demographic decline. Research Question: Do population flows respond to differences in local public service bundles under urban shrinkage?
Methods: MR-QAP (Multiple Regression Quadratic Assignment Procedure) Master’s Thesis (2018). A Study on the Reconceptualization of Sharing and a Case Analysis of the Sharing Economy (Written in Korean; Korean title: 공유의 재개념화와 공유경제 사례분석: 서울시 자동차 공유사례를 중심으로) This study examines collaboration at the community level, focusing on the concept of “sharing.” Since the 2010s, “sharing” has emerged as a prominent rhetorical device in marketing and public policy, often associated with notions of community and collective action. Seoul, the first city to officially declare itself a “Sharing City” in 2012, actively promoted policies and initiatives aimed at fostering a sharing culture. However, the concept of sharing remains analytically ambiguous and contested. To address this ambiguity, the study develops an ideal-typical framework of sharing and applies it to a case analysis of car-sharing in Seoul. Drawing on literature from anthropology, sociology, and business studies, the analysis distinguishes key dimensions of sharing—particularly patterns of behavior (including allocation and commoning practices) and states of possession and ownership—and examines their implications for understanding collaboration in urban communities. - Last updated: Feb. 2026
]]></description><link>2_research.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2_Research.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:45:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3_OtherActivities]]></title><link>3_otheractivities.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3_OtherActivities.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[9_CV]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Lee, M. &amp; Lee, J. (2025). Assessment of Jeju's Regional Conditions Using the Balanced National Development Index and Policy Implications. Society for Jeju Studies. 64. 223-246. 10.47520/jjs.2025.64.223. Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Merriman, D., Hu, X., Lee, J., Worthington, P.&nbsp;(2026).&nbsp;Current Condition and Future Concerns for Growth in Illinois’ State
Merriman, D., Funderburg, R. Hu, H., Lee, J, Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Worthington, P. (2025) The State of Illinois’ FY 2024 Fiscal Situation: A Solid Performance but Threats Remain.&nbsp;<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588" target="_self">https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588</a>
최태림, 김정욱, 이자훈. (2021). 인천광역시 일자리 사업 성과평가시스템 구축, 인천광역시.
김정욱, 이왕기, 이자훈. (2021). 인천광역시 제2기 마을공동체 만들기 기본계획, 인천광역시.
김정욱, 장정연, 이자훈, 이연정. (2020). 미추홀구 마을공동체 중간지원조직 운영방안, 인천연구원・미추홀구.
]]></description><link>9_cv.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9_CV.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3_Other Activities]]></title><link>3_other-activities.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3_Other Activities.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>