<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jahun Lee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Jahun Lee</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:45:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:45:55 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[HOME]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a Ph.D. Student in Public Administration at <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://cuppa.uic.edu/academics/pa" target="_self">the Department of Public Policy, Management and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago (UIC)</a>. I am an affiliated student of the Networks and Governance Lab at UIC.Hi! My name is Jahun Lee, and&nbsp;I am an Ph.D. Student in the Department of Public Policy, Management, and Analytics at the University of Illinois Chicago. My research focuses on urban governance, in particular, how local governments interact with others, including other governments, private organizations, particularly nonprofits, to enhance their performance and improve outcomes for their communities. Currently, I have interests in the influence of demographic shifts on urban governance. ]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2_Research]]></title><description><![CDATA[ My research primarily focuses on urban governance which involves various choices of different actors. Particularly, I concentrate on collaborations between local governments and third parties to understand patterns and mechanisms in urban contexts. Why Urban shrinkage? Figure 1. Map of Research Interests and Projects
Title: (TBD) - The Choice of Service Delivery Mode Title: A Study on the Reconceptualization of Sharing and a Case Analysis of the Sharing Economy (공유의 재개념화와 공유경제 사례분석: 서울시 자동차 공유사례를 중심으로)
Advisor: Dr. Tae Young Kim
Year: 2018
Sharing has become a rhetorical device in marketing and public policy, as it carries connotations of community. The concept of “sharing” generates confusion in public policy because it has multiple and ambiguous meanings. This study explores the concept of sharing, develops an ideal type of “sharing,” and analyzes the case of car-sharing in Seoul using this framework. Lee, M. &amp; Lee, J. (2025). Assessment of Jeju's Regional Conditions Using the Balanced National Development Index and Policy Implications. Society for Jeju Studies. 64. 223-246. 10.47520/jjs.2025.64.223. Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Merriman, D., Hu, X., Lee, J., Worthington, P.&nbsp;(2026).&nbsp;Current Condition and Future Concerns for Growth in Illinois’ State
Merriman, D., Funderburg, R. Hu, H., Lee, J, Wilbur-Mujtaba, A., Worthington, P. (2025) The State of Illinois’ FY 2024 Fiscal Situation: A Solid Performance but Threats Remain.&nbsp;<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588" target="_self">https://doi.org/10.25417/uic.29873588</a>
최태림, 김정욱, 이자훈. (2021). 인천광역시 일자리 사업 성과평가시스템 구축, 인천광역시.
김정욱, 이왕기, 이자훈. (2021). 인천광역시 제2기 마을공동체 만들기 기본계획, 인천광역시.
김정욱, 장정연, 이자훈, 이연정. (2020). 미추홀구 마을공동체 중간지원조직 운영방안, 인천연구원・미추홀구.
]]></description><link>2_research.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2_Research.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3_Other Activities]]></title><link>3_other-activities.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3_Other Activities.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1_About]]></title><description><![CDATA[Test pages
title: University of Illinois Chicago
date: Aug. 2021 - Current
description: Ph.D. in Public Administration title: University of Seoul
date: Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2018
description: Master in Public Administration ]]></description><link>1_about.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1_About.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>